<Root xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance" xmlns:xsd="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema" Name="Project" Version="1" xsi:noNamespaceSchemaLocation="http://aodevs.com/xsd/Project.v1.xsd">
  <Name>Demoders PlanetMap Viewer</Name>
  <Tagline>
    See ingame maps outside the game! Are you a multilogger? Demoders PlanetMap Viewer can track multiple characters simultaniously.
  </Tagline>
  <Description>
    Demoders PlanetMap Viewer lets you explore planet maps for Anarchy Online without logging in. If you are logged in to the game, it will plot your character(s) on the planet map.[br]The long-term goal is to be a full substitute to the ingame planetmap viewer.[br]
    [b]Features[/b]
    - Plot character marker on planet map for all locally running AO clients[br]
    - Smart camera tracking of multiple (selectable) characters[br]
    - [b]Overlay mode[/b] (F12)[br]
    [ulist]
    [*]Window will remain on top of other windows, such as Anarchy Online
    [*]Minimal footprint on screen real estate
    [*]An extensive menu becomes available upon right-click of the title bar
    [/ulist]
    - [b]Fullscreen mode[/b] (F11)[br]
    [ulist]
    [*]Optimal for running on a dedicated display
    [*]Window is maximized
    [*]Borders are removed
    [/ulist]
  </Description>
  <License>GPLv2</License>
  <Games>
    <Game>Anarchy Online</Game>
  </Games>
  <Pages>
    <Page Label="Known Issues">
      [b]Overlay mode fails to stay on top of Anarchy Online[/b]: There's a workaround available. Open the options dialog (tools->options) and enable the "Force on top (bugfix)" checkbox.[br]
      [b]No character tracking!?[/b][br] 
      This is probably caused by the PlanetMap Viewer being run as a non-administrative account, as the character tracking implementation requires administrative privilieges.[br]
      To force administrative privilieges, right-click the icon and chose "Run as administrator".[br]
      PMV accepts running as a non-administrative user because some users may not be interested in character tracking.      
    </Page>
    <Page Label="Credits">
      Created by Demoder (demoder@demoder.me)[br]
      See http://demoder.me/pmv/ for more information.[br]
      [br]
      Map plotting algorithm:[br]
      Thanks to Vhab for turning a huge amount of data points into a formula which is useable to do accurate plotting on the map.[br]
      Also thanks to Niniko for providing documentation on some of the concepts involved in this process.[br]
      [br]
      Icon:[br]
      Thanks to Vhab for creating the icon, and to Onack for giving permission to use AoRK for icon generation.[br]
      [br]
      Testing:[br]
      Thanks to Iriche, Vhab, Phooy, Jandorith and Nesual for extensive testing.[br]
    </Page>
  </Pages>
  <Staff>
    <Member Position="Author" Name="Demoder" Server="Rimor"/>
  </Staff>
  <Links>
    <Link Label="Website" Url="http://demoder.me/pmv/" />
    <Link Label="Bitbucket" Url="https://bitbucket.org/Savagedlight/demoder.planetmapviewer"/>
  </Links>
  <Versions>
    <LocalVersion Type="Stable" Value="1.0.0" Package="1.3.1"/>
  </Versions>
  <Packages>
    <!--
    <Package Name="hg-trunk">
      <Link Label="Nightly Builds" Url="http://build.vhabot.net/ccnet/server/win32/project/Vha.Chat/PackageList.aspx"/>
      <Repository Type="Mercurial" Label="Source" Url="https://bitbucket.org/Vhab/vha.chat/src/default"/>
    </Package>
    -->
    <Package Name="1.0.0" Date="2012-03-24">
      <File Label="Binaries" Url=""/>
      <File Label="Setup" Url=""/>
      <Repository Type="Subversion" Label="Source" Url=""/>
    </Package>
  </Packages>
</Root>
